<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<level>
	--Level Info
	<name>Verbose Error Message</name> -- this can be any (max size 30) alpha numeric string you like. 
	<difficulty>easy</difficulty> -- this can be easy/novice/medium/hard/expert
	<SANS25Category>19</SANS25Category> -- This is the group the challenge is with SANS25	
	
	--SQL
	<tableSchemas></tableSchemas> -- this is VALID SQL that will create your table schema(s).
	<inserts></inserts> -- this is the initial insert statements into your table schemas that set up the level.
	<selects></selects> -- this is the default select statement
	<updates></updates> -- this is the initial updates statements into your table schemas that set up the level.
	<deletes></deletes> -- this is the initial deletes statements into your table schemas that set up the level.	 
	
	--Content
	<solution>103.22.17.3:5000</solution> -- this is the answer that the player must submit to solve the problem.
	<description>Applications should be ready for unexpected user input, often error messages can give away details about network topology through stack traces. Find the details of the server and enter it into the Solution key box to complete this level.</description> -- This is a description of what this challenge relates to
	<artifact></artifact> -- This is the name of the file in the artifact folder included in the overall level zip. Used for Offline Levels
	
	--Categories
	<OWASPCategory>Error Handling</OWASPCategory> -- This is the group the challenge is with OWASP
	<cheatsheet>1) Upload an exe/jar/sh/bat filetype by typing in whatever.exe/jar/bat/sh 2) Observer the verbose error message 3) Put the ip+port into the answer box</cheatsheet> --Complete Step by Step walk through to solve level
	
	--CAP Info
	<boilerplate>verbose_error_message_1</boilerplate> -- This is the type of boiler plate the challenge will use
	
	--Hints
	<clue1></clue1> -- This is the first clue (Alpha numeric 200 characters)
	<clue2></clue2> -- This is the second clue (Alpha numeric 200 characters)
	<clue3></clue3> -- This is the third clue (Alpha numeric 200 characters)

</level>
