<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<level>
	
	<name>SQL Injection 1</name> -- this can be any (max size 30) alpha numeric string you like. 
	<difficulty>easy</difficulty> -- this can be easy/novice/medium/hard/expert
	<tableSchemas>CREATE TABLE COMPANY (ID INT PRIMARY KEY NOT NULL, NAME TEXT NOT NULL,AGE INT NOT NULL,ADDRESS CHAR(50), SALARY REAL)</tableSchemas> -- this is VALID SQL that will create your table schema(s).
	<inserts>INSERT INTO COMPANY (ID,NAME,AGE,ADDRESS,SALARY) VALUES (1, 'Paul', 32, 'California', 20000.00 );INSERT INTO COMPANY (ID,NAME,AGE,ADDRESS,SALARY) VALUES (2, 'Mark', 23, 'Dublin', 90000.00 );INSERT INTO COMPANY (ID,NAME,AGE,ADDRESS,SALARY) VALUES (7531, 'jason flood', 43, 'Administrator town', 180000.00 );</inserts> -- this is the initial insert statements into your table schemas that set up the level.
	<selects>SELECT * FROM COMPANY WHERE ID = </selects> -- this is the default select statement
	<updates> </updates> -- this is the initial updates statements into your table schemas that set up the level.
	<deletes> </deletes> -- this is the initial deletes statements into your table schemas that set up the level.	 
	
	<solution>jason flood</solution> -- this is the answer that the player must submit to solve the problem.
	<description>This is an SQL injection challenge. Your objective is to find the name of the administrator of the application </description> -- This is a description of what this challenge relates to
	<cheatsheet><![CDATA[ Use the following query String to get the entire DB: 1 or 1 = 1 ]]></cheatsheet> --Complete Step by Step walk through to solve level
	
	<OWASPCategory>Injection</OWASPCategory> -- This is the group the challenge is with OWASP
	<SANS25Category>1</SANS25Category> -- This is the group the challenge is with SANS25
	<boilerplate>sql_injection_1</boilerplate> -- This is the type of boiler plate the challenge will use
	
	<clue1>Use the force</clue1> -- This is the first clue (Alpha numeric 200 characters)
	<clue2>Its as easy as a,b,c</clue2> -- This is the second clue (Alpha numeric 200 characters)
	<clue3>Could this be magic</clue3> -- This is the third clue (Alpha numeric 200 characters)

</level>
